{
    "subject": "resource/Smart_Personal_Objects_Technology",
    "predicate": "http://purl.org/dc/terms/subject",
    "object": "resource/Category:2002_introductions",
    "human_readable": "Smart Personal Objects Technology is about 2002 introductions.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8517439365386963,
            "question": "When was Smart Personal Objects Technology introduced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.772835910320282,
            "question": "What technological advancement is associated with the year 2002?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7673529386520386,
            "question": "What year marked the beginning of Smart Personal Objects Technology?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6888845562934875,
            "question": "Around what time period did Smart Personal Objects Technology emerge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6841034889221191,
            "question": "What innovations might have been happening around the time Smart Personal Objects Technology was introduced?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6237931251525879,
            "question": "What does 'Smart Personal Objects Technology' refer to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6121413111686707,
            "question": "Can you describe the concept of Smart Personal Objects Technology?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5593468546867371,
            "question": "What are some examples of Smart Personal Objects Technology?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5041560530662537,
            "question": "What future developments can we anticipate in the field of Smart Personal Objects Technology?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4559289216995239,
            "question": "How has Smart Personal Objects Technology influenced our lives?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Smart Personal Objects Technology is about 2002 introductions.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3159_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What future developments can we anticipate in the field of Smart Personal Objects Technology?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3159_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What are some examples of Smart Personal Objects Technology?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3159_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you describe the concept of Smart Personal Objects Technology?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3159_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3159_121.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3159_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3159_26.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3159_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3159_37.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3159_50.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3159_52.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3159_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3159_82.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3159_97.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the JSON response:\n\n```\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports that Smart Personal Objects Technology (SPOT) was indeed introduced around 2002, as stated in file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3159/re-ranker-msmarco/26.txt and file_path /Users/stefanomarchesin/Research/fshami/Rag/docs/dbpedia_3159/re-ranker-msmarco/78.txt."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nExplanation: The documents mention that Microsoft introduced the Smart Personal Object Technology (SPOT) in 2002, which aligns with the query stating that SPOT is about 2002 introductions."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}